{
    "subject": "Mongkut",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Debsirindra",
    "human_readable": "Mongkut is married to Debsirindra.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9563754200935364,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the marriage of Mongkut and Debsirindra?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9450076222419739,
            "question": "Is there a relationship between Mongkut and Debsirindra?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8815294504165649,
            "question": "Name someone who is married to Debsirindra."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8633512258529663,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Mongkut and Debsirindra?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.856896162033081,
            "question": "Who is married to Debsirindra?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8408805131912231,
            "question": "Is Debsirindra married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8168922662734985,
            "question": "Who is Mongkut's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7568884491920471,
            "question": "Is Mongkut in a marital relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6799436211585999,
            "question": "What is the name of Mongkut's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6129880547523499,
            "question": "Who is Mongkut?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Mongkut is married to Debsirindra.",
            "html": "yago_23358_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Mongkut's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_23358_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Mongkut in a marital relationship?",
            "html": "yago_23358_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Mongkut's wife?",
            "html": "yago_23358_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23358_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23358_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23358_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23358_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23358_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23358_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23358_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23358_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23358_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23358_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the structured JSON format for the query:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents support the triple that Mongkut (Rama IV) was married to Debsirindra, as mentioned in multiple files (e.g., file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_23358/re-ranker-msmarco/45.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_23358/re-ranker-msmarco/74.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Queen Debsirindra was the second consort of King Mongkut (Rama IV), and that she gave birth to Prince Chulalongkorn. This information supports the statement that Mongkut is married to Debsirindra."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}